xcite.com.sa 2017-08-15

# Xcite by Alghanim International KSA | Privacy Policy

#### (Updated 23 August 2015)

Alghanim International Electronics, owner of www.xcite.com.sa website (“ **Website** ”), respects your privacy, and seeks to comply with applicable legal requirements in respect of data collection, processing and transfer. By using www.xcite.com.sa or the Services offered through www.xcite.com.sa (and thus accepting the **Terms of Use** ), you expressly consent to Alghanim International Electronics using your Information, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Website is subject to your acceptance of the Terms of Use of www.xcite.com.sa and this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the Terms and this Privacy Policy, then you must discontinue your use of [www.xcite.com.sa](http://www.xcite.com.sa/).

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of Registered Users and visitors who use or visit www.xcite.com.sa. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to detail the manner in which we use your information, including your personal information that we may obtain about you, during your use of [www.xcite.com.sa](http://www.xcite.com.sa/ "xcite.com").

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling that to others. We share the information collected by us, only as described below and with the Group companies/subsidiaries/affiliates of Alghanim International Electronics, that either are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Collecting Personal Information and its use:

1\. In the course of your use of www.xcite.com.sa, you provide us with certain information, as mentioned below (collectively referred to as the “ **Personal Information** ”), which we may collect, store and use for providing the Services and performing our contractual obligations, other than allowing us to better understand the Website users and improve the layout and functionality of [www.xcite.com.sa](http://www.xcite.com.sa/ "xcite.com.sa");

  * Information about your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, billing and credit/debit/charge card information, order history, feedback, about your visits to and use of www.xcite.com.sa (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views, and website navigation etc.)
  * Information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to www.xcite.com.sa, including information relating to any purchases you make of our Products or Services.
  * Information that you provide to us for registering with us as a Registered User (including your Account details).
  * Information that you provide to us for subscribing to [www.xcite.com.sa](http://www.xcite.com.sa/ "xcite.com") Services, e-mail notifications, and/or newsletters.
  * Any other information that you choose to send to us; and feedback including Product/Service reviews.

2\. We may use the Personal Information that you provide or that is obtained by us:

  * To register you with [www.xcite.com.sa](http://www.xcite.com.sa/ "xcite.com.sa") and to administer and provide our Services, as mentioned on www.xcite.com.sa.
  * To fulfill our agreement of providing Services to you, including those relating to your purchase of Products and their processing and obtaining payment;
  * To analyze and profile your shopping preferences (market, customer and product analysis etc.) to enable us to review, develop and improve the Products and Services we offer and to enable us to provide you and other customers with relevant information through our marketing programs. We may use your Personal Information to make decisions about your using computerized technology, for example automatically selecting Products and Services which we think will interest you from the information we have. We may keep you informed of such Products and Services including special offers, discounts, offers, competitions and so on (including products and services of other companies and organizations) by e-mail, telephone (including automated calls),SMS text messages and other electronic messages such as picture messaging, post, fax or otherwise.
  * When you provide us with your information, you will be given the option to mention if you do not wish to receive information of such products and services from either us or carefully chosen third parties; and to administer any prize draws or competitions you may wish to enter.

3\. We may supplement the Personal Information that you provide to us with information that we receive from third parties (e.g., credit reference agencies).

#### Fraud Prevention

4\. In order to protect our customers and us from fraud and theft, we may share all or any of the Personal Information that we obtain (for confirming identity and other information in our customer records, including how you conduct your Account etc.), with other Group companies/subsidiaries/affiliates of Alghanim International Electronics, other third parties, companies, retailers and to financial and other organizations (including law enforcement agencies) involved in fraud prevention and detection, to use in the same way.

#### Telephone Calls

5\. All Telephone calls (incoming/outgoing) may be recorded to verify content and may be used together with your records for regulatory compliance, quality control, and staff training, preventing, or detecting criminal activity and for complaint resolution.

#### Disclosure of Your Information

6\. While we will make every effort to safeguard and keep confidential the information provided to us, we might share your Personal Information with other Group companies/subsidiaries/affiliates of Alghanim International Electronics and other third parties, companies, retailers and organizations whose services or Products we provide to you through [www.xcite.com.sa](http://www.xcite.com.sa/ "xcite.com.sa"), for the following reasons:

  * To other companies and organizations to administer any prize draws or competitions.
  * To our agents, staff and approved third parties to provide services for us.
  * To anyone to whom we assign or transfer our rights and duties under our agreement with you.
  * If we have a duty to do so or if the law compels us to do so either in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; or in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).

7\. In carrying out the activities specified in this section, we may transfer Personal Information to reputable organizations or companies outside Kuwait. We take steps to ensure that your information will be accorded the same level of protection as that required of us under applicable Kuwait law. By agreeing to the Terms and this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to such sharing of Personal Information.

8\. If Alghanim International Electronics is sold to a third party or Alghanim International Electronics otherwise becomes subject of a merger, consolidation or acquisition, it would become necessary for us to transfer your Personal Information to a third party, and in such case Alghanim would require that the third party handles your Personal Information with no less care than taken by us.

#### Cookies

9\. New technologies are emerging on the Internet that help us deliver customized visitor experience. Alghanim International Electronics may use such new technologies, including cookies or other technologies, to remember your information when you use www.xcite.com.sa. We may use such technologies for tracking activity on www.xcite.com.sa, preparing reports, assessing trends, and otherwise monitoring the way in which www.xcite.com.sa is being used. By accepting the Terms of use of www.xcite.com.sa and this Privacy Policy, you confirm your consent to Alghanim International Electronics use of cookies, and other such technologies, for these purposes. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block all cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored.

#### Security

10\. We take all steps reasonably necessary to protect against unauthorized access, use, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of Personal Information. Any information that we collect and store that is personally identifiable is protected using appropriate means, and Alghanim International Electronics is not responsible for any unauthorized access or use by third parties, unless such access is enabled because of our gross negligence or willful misconduct.

11\. Protecting your Personal Information is very important to us. Therefore, we take the following precautions, among others, to better protect the Personal Information;

  * We take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of your Personal Information including the use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. Our website is certified by VeriSign and transactions managed through our partnership with KNET and Gulf Bank.
  * We store all the Personal Information you provide to us on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.
  * We display only the last four digits of your credit/debit card numbers, whilst in case of the use of Visa or MasterCard the CVV number will be requested, and when using KNet cards you will be required to enter your Knet pin when confirming an order. However, the entire card number will need to be given to the appropriate Card Company (Knet or MiGS) during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your Account and password and to your computer. You must ensure that you log out/ sign-off from your Account, when you are exiting [www.xcite.com.sa](http://www.xcite.com.sa/ "xcite.com.sa")

#### Product reviews

12\. It is possible that two weeks after receiving your Product, we may send you an e-mail inviting you to review and rate the Products that you have purchased. In addition, sometimes we may also ask you if you would like to answer questions related to your Product, as submitted by other customers.

You may note that:

  * Your review may be shared on other Alghanim International Electronics company/subsidiary/affiliate websites.
  * Once submitted, it usually takes 72 hours for your review, question or answer to appear on www.xcite.com.sa provided it is in line with our publishing guidelines
  * Your review can be submitted anonymously or if you prefer, you can leave a ratings only review.
  * It is not possible for you to edit/remove your review after submission.

If you require any further information on this service or wish to have your review removed, you can contact Customer Services.

#### General

13\. You have the option to receive a copy of the Personal Information that we retain about you. Provision of such information will be subject to:

  * Receipt of a written request from you;
  * The supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a certified photocopy of your passport or civil identification card plus an original of a utility bill showing your current address).

14\. We may withhold such Personal Information to the extent permitted by law.

15\. You may instruct us not to process your Personal Information for marketing purposes by e-mail at any time. If you are concerned that any of the Personal Information that we hold is inaccurate, you may Contact Us.

16\. Our Website may contain links to other websites. Alghanim International Electronics is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites not operated by Alghanim International Electronics. We encourage users to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects Personal Information.

17\. You may receive emails from X-cite by Alghanim International Electronics based on your subscription request. If you wish at any time to unsubscribe, you may click the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email communication.

18\. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on [www.xcite.com,sa](http://www.xcite.com.sa/ "xcite.com.sa") and with respect to any Personal Information and other information we collect in the future, will become effective as of the date of posting (see date posted above). It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure you are aware of any changes. We may also notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy by e-mail.

#### Contact Us

If you have any comments or queries in connection with our Terms and/or Privacy Policy, you can contact us by sending an email on [info@xcite.com.sa](mailto:info@xcite.com.sa) or call our customer service at 8004333334. Address: Al-Riyad 11361, Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, P.O. Box 30514
